Let's add a little bit of natspec to make this look even more professional
让我们添加一些自然语言规范("natspec")来让我们的合约更专业一些
and and give people who are reading our contract even more information.
同时也为了给阅读我们合约的人们提供更多的信息
So let's add title here at title and we'll say a sample raffle contract
让我们先添加一个标题 `@title A sample Raffle Contract` (“标题：一个抽奖合约示例”)
will say an author is going to be me Patrick Collins or
然后是 `@author` (“作者”)也就是我 `Patrick Collins`
you can put your own name there as well
或者你也可以写你自己的名字
at notice. This contract is for creating and untampered orrible decentralized smart contract.
`@notice This contract is for creating an untamperable decentralized smart contract`
(“说明：本合约旨在创建一个不可篡改的去中心化智能合约”)
And then we'll do add Dev, this implements chain link VRF v two, and chain link keepers.
接下来是 `@dev This implements Chainlink VRF v2 and Chainlink Keepers`
(“对开发者：实现了 Chainlink VRF v2 以及 Chainlink Keepers”)
Alright, awesome. We've got our type declarations,
非常好，我们已经有了 "Type declarations" (“类型声明”)
we've got our state variables,
还有了 "State Variables"(“状态变量”)
we've got lottery variables, which are still state variables,
还有了 "Lottery Variables"(“抽奖变量”)，它们也是状态变量的一部分
we've got our events. Now it's time for our functions. Afterwards,
我们还已经有了 "Events"(“事件”)，现在该轮到我们的 "Functions"(“函数”)了
we've done a little bit of natspec, at least on our check upkeep.
我们已经在这一部分写了一些 natspec 了，至少在 "checkUpkeep" 这里是的
If you want to add some more natspec on things like enter, raffle, perform upkeep, etc,
如果你想要添加一些更多的 natspec 比如说 "enterRaffle", "performUpkeep" 等等
you can absolutely do so. And then down at the bottom, we have our views slash pure getter functions.
当然是可以这样做的，先拉到下面，我们有一些 "View / Pure" 类型的 "getter" 函数
Let's see, do we want any other getter functions here?
我们看一下，还需要别的 "getter" 函数么？
Well, we probably want to give people the chance to get a raffle state.
我们应该还需要为人们提供一个获取抽奖状态的方法
So we'll do function, get raffle state, this will be a public, you returns a raffle state.
所以创建一个 `function getRaffleState() public view returns (RaffleState)`
We'll say return s underscore raffle state,
接着是 `return s_raffleState`
we probably want to give people the chance to get the number of words.
我们还需要给人们提供一个获取随机数数量的方法
And this is going to be a little bit interesting here
这件事其实还挺有意思的
running. So if we do function, get num words, public view returns, you went to the six
开始吧 `function getNumWords() public view returns(uint256)`
return num words, you'll see something interesting happened here.
`return NUM_WORDS` 你将会看到一些有趣的事发生
We pull up our compiler and run hh compile.
我们打开编译器，运行 `hh compile`
Hopefully everything works here.
希望一切运行正常
Oh, and everything doesn't work because I didn't import this correctly.
哦，并没有正常运行，因为这里的导入不正确
Let's fix that. Let's try again.
把它改正，再试一次
Oh, there's a couple things I missed. Let's fix es players.
哦，这里还有一些错误，把它改成 `s_players`
This is why it's good to compile as you code
这就是为什么最好要在编写代码的时候多进行编译
as players dot length. Let's try again.
改成 "players.length" 再试一次
And I spelt interval wrong.
"interval" 拼错了（笑）
I underscore inter vol strike to compile again,
`i_interval` 再编译一次
see how many more spelling mistakes I made. And there it is.
看一下还有没有其它拼写错误，是有的
I underscore in error go to paste that
`i_in` 错误在这，粘贴上去
and we do get another error here.
这里还有另外一处错误
Invalid type for argument in a function call
函数调用中的参数类型无效
invalid implicit conversion from literal string to bytes called data requested.
从字面字符串 "" 到 "bytes calldata" 的请求存在无效的隐式转换
Since we're passing this empty string here. And checkup keep needs a call data
这是由于我们在这里传入了一个空字符串，而 "checkUpkeep" 需要的是一个 calldata
called data actually doesn't work with strings.
calldata 不能使用字符串
So we need to make this bytes memory instead. And our compiler is now happy with us.
所以我们需要把这里替换为 `bytes memory`，这下我们的编译应该可以通过了
And I spell it the timestamp wrong. That's a lowercase s
这里的 "timestamp" 拼错了，应该是小写的 "s"
so and you might see some squiggles here on Check upkeep,
你可能会注意到 "checkUpkeep" 这里有一些波浪线
we could make this a view function since we're not actually modifying any state.
我们可以把它变成一个 "view" 函数，因为我实际上并没有修改任何状态
But I want to keep it public for reasons I'll show you a little bit later.
但我仍然会把它设置为 public，原因我稍后会向你展示
But finally we get the the yellow squiggly that I was looking for here.
最终我们还是得到了这些黄色的波浪线
And if we run hh compile, we should see a warning in our compiler as well.
如果我们运行 `hh compile`，应该会在编译器里看到这些警告
Okay, so we see all those yellow squigglies here.
好的，我们在这里看到了所有的黄色波浪线
Unnamed return variable can remain unassigned.
未命名的返回变量可以保持未分配状态
We need this bytes memory in here because that's what the keepers are looking for.
我们需要保留这个 "bytes memory" 因为这是 Keepers 所需要的
Morning function state mutability can be restricted to view for our function checkup key.
警告：函数的状态可变性可限制为 "view"，说的是我们的函数 "checkUpkeep"
You can make a view if you want, but I'm
going to keep it public for reasons I'll show you a little
bit later. And finally, function state mutability can be
restricted to pure this is what I wanted to show you since num
words is actually in the bytecode, since it's a constant
variable technically isn't reading from storage, and
therefore this can be a pure function. Returning num words
doesn't actually read in storage, it literally will go
and read the number one. So doing get num words in solidity
with num words being a constant variable, it's going to
literally be the exact same as saying get one and we would
return one here, we might also want to get the number of
players. So we'll create a function get number of players.
And this will be a public view, returns a un 256. Turn s
underscore players dot length. We're also probably going to
want the latest timestamp. So we'll do function get latest
timestamp. public view returns you in 256. And we're just going
to return s underscore last timestamp. And maybe we'll want
to do request confirmation. So we'll do function GET request
confirmations. Public pure since request confirmations is also a
constant function returns you went to you went to 56 Turn
request confirmations. All right, we've got some wonderful
getters here. Some views slash pure functions, we have a way to
get a random number we have a way in a decentralized context.
Automatic automatically execute. picking a random winner we have
a way for people to enter our raffle to enter this lottery.
And we have a bullet proof way to solve creating a truly fair
decentralized lottery. Oh my goodness. Let's do one more
compile for good measure H H compile. And these are just
warnings. So we're good to go here. Our code is compiling
successfully.